https://www.stripersonline.com/surftalk/privacy/

Privacy Policy
At StripersOnline, your privacy is extremely important to us - just like it always has been
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Log files are maintained and analyzed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do log IP addresses, file requests, browser type, operating system type and other non personally identifiable information that help us to make sure this is secure, functional and working with various combinations of browsers and operating systems.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured specifically to attract anyone under 13. We cannot be responsible for people that lie about their age, as kids are likely to do. As a parent, please be aware of your child's participation in any online community and all social media sites. If and when we become aware a person registered here is under 13 years old, they will be removed from the site immediately. If you, as a parent of a child under 13 years old wishes to allow your child to participate on this website, please contact me personally - tims@stripersonline.com - and I will explain how we can do that in a manner that protects this website and your child, legally.
Cookies
This website does not store any personally identifiable information about users of this service. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis, to maintain user preferences and to help us serve appropriate ads and control the distribution of those ads - again, these cookies contain no personally identifiable information about you.
Google Advertising Cookies may be used as well, depending on whether the page you are viewing is presently showing Google Ads or ads from a non-Google network. Google's description of their "advertising cookie" is:
Our main advertising cookie on non-Google sites is called ‘id’ and it is stored in browsers under the domain doubleclick.net. We use others with names such as _drt_, FLC, and exchange_uid.
Sometimes a cookie may be set on the domain of the site you are visiting. In the case of our DoubleClick product, a cookie called ‘__gads’ may be set on the domain of the site you are visiting.
Google also uses conversion cookies whose main purpose is to help advertisers determine how many times people who click on their ads end up purchasing their products. These cookies allow Google and the advertiser to determine that you clicked the ad and later visited the advertiser site. Conversion cookies are not used by Google for interest-based ad targeting and persist for a limited time only. Conversion cookie data may also be used in combination with your Google account to link conversion events across different devices you use. Only anonymous conversion data gathered from these cookies is shared with advertisers.
Google Analytics is also used on this site so we can understand where our traffic comes from, which pages visitors look at most, which pages visitors are most likely to leave after viewing, how many pages visitors view, how long they spend here, etc, etc. Again, any cookies used by this process contain no personally identifiable information. Here is Google's page explaining their Analytics cookies.
As we continue to develop this website and the advertising shown on it, we will continue to update this privacy policy page.
